So in afterwards, for tour, we'll ask me to select a style.
Please select three to 10 styles.
And these styles that we select will help for tour understand what we want more, you know,
and understand it better.
And at the end, the generated result will be way closer to what we are looking for.
So I wait until all these styles are loaded.
As you see, all of them styles are loaded, so we have professional, we have office,
we have ID photo, real estate, casual, bookshelf, you know, and you can choose from them,
right?
You can choose among them.
So let's say that I want to have my photo in, let's say, yearbook style, as well as
um, stylish, right?
And let's say, um, office or professional, it doesn't matter.
So yes, I choose these three styles, so as you see, the minimum is three and the maximum
is 10 styles.
And yes, I choose two indoors, I choose one, I chose one indoor and two studios.
But let me actually choose one outdoor, it will be better, I think.
So this one is also coming to be my choice.
And by clicking on continue.